SABRA AKHAVAN

FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

Sabraaa

sabraakhavan

sabraakhavaan@gmail.com

www.sabraakhavan.me

+98-921-405-3184

TECHNOLOGY

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, TypeScript, Tailwind, Sass Production and Version Control: Git, Github Deployment and Hosting: Netlify,

LANGUAGES

English C1 Deutsch B2

Vercel

EDUCATION

GUILAN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's degree in Genetics Biology 2020-2024

PROJECTS

SABRAS GPT-3

sabrasgpt.vercel.appFigma-based, responsive,created using React.js CSS andBEM methodology

MY PORTFOLIO

<u>sabraakhavan.me</u>
Figma-based, responsive,
created using React.js+Vite,
CSS and BEM methodology

ABOUT ME

As a front-end web developer since 2020, I've rapidly advanced from HTML & CSS to mastering various web technologies and practices, demonstrated in diverse projects. My passion lies in using programming to solve real-world problems and for creative expression. Committed to continuous learning and innovation, I am a valuable asset to any web development team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

Pejvak (2020 - 2021)

- Collaborated with designers to build a modern, responsive website to improve the user experience
- Collaborated with a team of developers to build modern, responsive web applications using best practices
- Developed web applications to facilitate the content management for non-developer admins

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Sitenova (2021)

- Collaborated with a team of frontend developers, backend developers and DevOps engineers on different projects
- Maintained and improved legacy projects Improved soft skills to facilitate communications and cooperations as a team player
- Worked alongside product owners to better understand the mission and envision it for the technical team
- designed and developed a comprehensive web applications

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Rayga-Rayane_Sadaf (2021 - 2023)

- Collaborated with a team of new recruits that helped elevate the firm
- Use of the scrum methodology to prioritise and execute tasks
- Improvement in the use of design patterns

SEO MANAGER

Markerting Planet (2024)

- Content management of English websites in the field of real estate consultant and financial management of Congaurd.ca Company located in Canada
- Mastered the structure of English SEO and communication with the user